[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] 30 minutes
after the extermination team
launched their offensive,
even as the fierce battle unfolded inside,
an immense number of citizens
who had been hypnotized
by Pouf's wing scales
were still lined up beyond the walls
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
BREAKDOWN X AND X AWAKENING
[electricity crackling]
Someone's watching me, and…
[footsteps pattering]
[gasps]
If Gon sees what's happened to Palm,
he's not gonna be able to handle it.
There's no room left inside of his heart,
not for something as awful as this.
[glass shatters]
…Gon could totally lose it.
I have to find out right here and now.
We still have a chance.
Palm approached me herself.
[Killua] I thought she could use
some kind of divination to locate people,
but it's probably closer to Clairvoyance.
And if Palm had changed sides,
she definitely would've backed off.
She approached me,
so she must remember me…
Killua, right?
[gasps]
[Killua] I knew it.
She does remember!
[Palm] Where's Gon?
[sighs]
Once he sees what I have become,
do you think that he's going to hate me?
[sighs] Gon doesn't judge people
by their appearances.
Also, you're assuming
he liked you in the first place.
You always act like
such a spiteful little brat,
now, don't you?
Gon is with Pitou at the moment.
I'm sure he's--
[tense music playing]
So was it just by chance you found me?
Huh? What are you talking about?
You were the one who just walked
around the corner and found me.
[Killua] You're wrong. I sensed you.
I felt you watching me,
and that's the reason I came this way.
But I'm sure you noticed me first.
Why are you lying?
[Palm] You are such a little pest.
Where is Gon?
Answer me first, and maybe I'll tell you.
Then she used Clairvoyance
to watch me follow her
Where can I find Gon?
I'm not telling you.
[Killua gasps]
[Palm] It seems I've made a mistake.
There are better ways to use my abilities.
[Killua] Damn. She's dangerous.
Better to let everything out,
don't you think?
A perfect example of that would be
my desire to kill you!
[laughs]
Well? What are you gonna do now?
Will you stay silent?
Give up and talk?
[Palm laughing]
[blows striking]
[narrator] Palm's ability, Black Widow,
turns her hair into a weapon
However, what made Black Widow frightening
[groans]
Whoa! Hey! Miss Palm, please,
you've gotta stop using your Hatsu!
[Killua] Palm is originally an Enhancer.
The difference it makes when your ability
is a perfect match is incredible.
If the fight drags on,
I'm totally done for.
But even so, I can't run away.
I can tell that Gon's mind
is already at its limit.
And while he sits there waiting for Pitou,
he's barely holding himself together.
[chuckles]
and if there is…
it's not gonna help.
[rumbling]
[groans]
Huh? Why are you asking now?
There's no reason, actually.
I just want to see him.
He's probably nearby.
Don't worry. I'll find him myself.
Just as soon as I've killed you, that is!
Sorry!
I panicked earlier,
and I called you the enemy.
You might look different,
but you're still Palm, aren't you?
[gasps]
That person had his soul taken away,
and right now, Gon is facing off
against the person who's responsible.
If he sees you now,
looking so different
than you did before…
[gasps]
Gon is gonna totally snap.
So when you see him…
make sure you call him by his name first.
That's it. That's my condition.
Before we entered the palace,
Gon was really worried about you.
He told me that himself.
So, please, give him some peace of mind.
[narrator] He was just buying time.
He had no intention of letting them meet,
at least, not at first.
[Killua crying]
[Killua] Please, if you can…
put his mind at ease.
Please, only you…
can do that now, Palm.
No one else…
can reach him.
It's all up to you now.
I just…
[continues wailing]
Look. He's defenseless.
So, new strategy, kill him now,
Number One.
[dramatic music playing]
Surrounded by the brutally evil aura,
she felt as though
she would soon be crushed to dust,
and, in an instant,
came to the very same conclusion
that Knov had.
Then as she watched Pouf slowly
and silently descend the stairs,
As one cannot help but shiver in the cold,
no one could blame Palm
for reflexively using her own aura
who agreed to forego a meal,
Pitou and Pouf made her
experimental soldier Number One.
Those who remembered their pasts
had shown stronger mental fortitude
than the others.
This phenomenon was most noticeable
in Ants who possessed Nen abilities.
It was becoming clear
that memories of the past
had a tendency to both assist
and deter the soldiers' growth.
to destroy the connection
between Palm's memories and her emotions.
The experiments on Cheetu and Leol
confirmed that those
who retained more of their memories
emerged from their cocoons
much sooner than their counterparts.
would be to leave soldiers
with their memories
while maintaining
strict control over them.
As it happened,
Palm was the perfect guinea pig.
The success of the experiment
Palm Siberia.
[gasps]
Don't call me "Number One"!
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
Thank you, Killua.
I owe it all to you.
and there was nothing I could do.
It was like that ever since I woke up.
[gasps]
If it means helping Gon,
I'm ready to do anything in my power.
But please don't forget,
[Shaiapouf groans]
[Menthuthuyoupi] What is it?
[Shaiapouf] Total failure,
and that's all there is to it.
[Menthuthuyoupi] Huh?
If it's soldiers I require,
I can create them on my own.
In fact, that will make it much easier
Wait. But this is mine.
Oh, well.
[singer singing in Japanese]